Guide to the H. Thomas Hickerson papers, 1974-2006.
Hickerson, H. Thomas papers,1972-2006.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
H. Thomas Hickerson papers, 1972-2006.
13-6-3122
H. Thomas. Hickerson
22.4 cubic ft.
Printed Materials, Correspondence, Financial Records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Alphabetical subject files documenting activities as chairman of the Department of Manuscripts and University Archives, and as Director of the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Archivist and library administrator.
H. Thomas Hickerson was Associate University Librarian for Information Technologies and Special Collections in the Cornell University Library. His special collections responsibilities included oversight for the Library's principal rare book and manuscript programs. He served in the Department of Manuscript and University Archives as Supervisor of Technical Operations from 1974 to 1979, and as Department Chair from 1979 to 1991. He directed the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections from 1992 through 1998. Tom was the founding director of the Cornell Institute for Digital Collections, established in 1997 and succeeding the Digital Access Coalition, which he organized in 1992. He is a former president of the Society of American Archivists and has served on SAA Council, on the National Information Systems Task Force, and was the first chair of the Society's Standards Board, among other SAA groups. He was named a Fellow of the Society in 1987. Additionally, he was the first chair of the Research Libraries Group's Task Force on Archives, Manuscripts, and Special Collections, served on the Executive Committee of the ALA Rare Books and Manuscripts Section, and co-chaired the ALA/SAA Joint Committee on Library-Archives Relations. He holds B.A. and M.A. degrees from the University of Oklahoma and previously directed the Oklahoma State Archives and Records Division of the State Library.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Alphabetical subject files documenting activities as chairman of the Dept. of Manuscripts and University Archives, and as Director of the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, relating to all aspects of administration. Includes files relating to the building of the Carl A. Kroch Library and the beginnings of the Digital Access Coalition (DAC), especially the Museum Educational Site Licensing project (MESL). Also, chronologically arranged files documenting his professional involvement in organizations including the Society of American Archivists (SAA), its National Information Systems Task Force (NISTF), and the SAA Council; the ALA/SAA Joint Committee on Library-Archives Relations; and various committees and task forces of the Research Libraries Group (RLG).
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hickerson, H. Thomas.; American Library Association.ALA SAA Joint Committee on Library-Archives Relations.; Carl A. Kroch Library (Cornell University); Cornell University.Dept. of Manuscripts and University Archives.; Cornell University.Library.Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections.; Research Libraries Group.; Society of American Archivists.; Society of American Archivists.Council.; Society of American Archivists.Standards Board.; Society of American Archivists.National Information Systems Task Force.
Subjects:
Libraries--Special collections--Administration.; Library administration.; Archives--Administration.; Archivists.; Library administrators.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Budget and personnel files are restricted to permission of the donor and to the director of the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections.
All other seriesare restricted to permission of the donor for ten years.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Subject files are arranged alphabetically. Organizational files are arranged chronologically.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I: Subject Files and Correspondence
  - Alphabetical Subject Files A-H: M&A / RMC (Box 1)
  - Alphabetical Subject Files H-N: M&A / RMC (Box 2)
  - Alphabetical Subject Files N-W: M&A / RMC (Box 3)
  - Alphabetical Subject Files A-H: RMC (Box 3)
  - Alphabetical Subject Files H-W: M&A / RMC (Box 4)
  - Financial Records: M&A / RMC (Box 5)
  - Kroch Library Building Project (Box 6)
  - Subseries I: Department of Manuscripts and University Archives (M&A) / Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections (RMC)
    - Academy of Certified Archivists, 1994-1995 (Box 13)
    - ACRL National Convention, 1997 (Box 13)
    - ACRL Program, 1997 (Box 13)
    - ACRL, Western NY/Ontario, 1998 (Box 13)
    - ALA Annual Meeting, 1998 (Box 13)
    - ALA Midwinter, 1998 (Box 13)
    - ALA Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 13)
    - ALA Annual Meeting, 1996 (Box 13)
    - ALA Midwinter, Feb. 1995 (Box 13)
    - ALA-LITA Presentation, 1994 (Box 13)
    - ALA Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 13)
    - ALA/RBMS Program, 1994 (Box 13)
    - ALA Midwinter, 1994 (Box 13)
    - ACA (Academy of Certified Archivists) August Meeting, 1993 (Box 13)
    - ALA Midwinter, Jan 1993 (Box 13)
    - ALA Summer Meeting, 1992 (Box 13)
    - American Library Association (Box 13)
    - ALA-ALCTS Preconference, 1993 (Box 13)
    - ALA/RBMC Presentation, 1993 (Box 13)
    - American Archivist (Box 13)
    - AMIGOS (Box 13)
    - ASIS (American Society of Information Scientists), 1993 (Box 13)
    - Bancroft Library, Director of, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Bearman, David, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Bentley Historical Library, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Bentley Symposium, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Bentley Symposium, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Bentley Fellowship, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Bentley Seminar, 1990 (Box 13)
    - California, Irvine HTH (Box 13)
    - CNI Spring Meeting, 1998 (Box 13)
    - DeWitt Historial Society, 1991 (Box 13)
    - DHP Workshop, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Dimunation, Mark, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Dooley, Jackie, 1996 (Box 13)
    - EDUCUM, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Engst Report, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Harvard Project, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Harvard Project June Meeting, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Houghton Library Conference, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Houghton Library, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Interlibrary Loan Committee (ILL), 1994 (Box 13)
    - Imaging Workshops, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Ithaca Centennial - History Committee, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Kenney, Anne R., 1985 (Box 13)
    - Laurence, Katherine, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Library Trends Article, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Lake Ontario Archives Conference (LOAC), 1988 (Box 13)
    - LOAC, 1989 (Box 13)
    - LOAC, 1990 (Box 13)
    - LOAC, 1991 (Box 13)
    - LOAC, 1992 (Box 14)
    - LOAC, 1993 (Box 14)
    - MARAC Paper (Box 14)
    - MARAC Fall Meeting, 1990 (Box 14)
    - Meckler Conference, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Midwestern Archivist - Book Reviews, 1987 (Box 14)
    - New York State Research Libraries, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Nilan, Roxanne (Box 14)
    - Palm, Charles, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Rare Books and Manuscript Librarianship, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Southern Methodist University (SMU), 1997 (Box 14)
    - SOLINET Annual Meeting, May 1996 (Box 14)
    - SAA Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 14)
    - SAA Summer Meeting, 1998 (Box 14)
    - Rare Books and Manuscripts Section (RBMS), 1994-1995 (Box 14)
    - RBMS, Midwinter, 1994 (Box 14)
    - RBMS, 1995-1996 (Box 14)
    - RBMS Paper, 1996 (Box 14)
    - RBMS Preconference, 1993 (Box 14)
    - RBMS Preconference, 1996 (Box 14)
    - RBMS Preconference, 1996 (Box 14)
    - RBMS Program Brochure (Box 14)
    - RBMS Executive Committees, 1994 (Box 14)
    - RBMS Executive Committee Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 14)
    - RBMS Executive Committee Meeting, February 1995 (Box 14)
    - RBMS Executive Committee Meeting, June 1995 (Box 14)
    - RBMS Executive Committee Meeting, July 1996 (Box 14)
    - RBMS Executive Committee Midwinter Meeting, 1996 (Box 14)
    - RBMS Membership Committee (ad hoc) (Box 14)
    - Art and Architecture Thesaurus (AAT), 1984 (Box 14)
    - ACRL Papers, 1984 (Box 14)
    - ALA, June 1983 (Box 14)
    - ALA Presentation, 1979 (Box 14)
    - ACRL Conference - Seattle, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Bearman, David (Box 14)
    - Book Review - Midwestern Archivist (Box 14)
    - Baltimore Region Institutional Studies Center (BRISC), 1982 (Box 14)
    - University of Western Ontario Cooperative Document, 1978 (Box 14)
    - Harvard NHPRC Proposal, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Hensen Review (Box 14)
    - Hoover Institution (Box 14)
    - LOAC Paper, 1981 (Box 14)
    - LOAC, 1995 (Box 14)
    - LOAC, 1981 (Box 14)
    - MARAC, Fall 1980 (Box 14)
    - MARAC / NEA - Albany (Box 14)
    - MARC - Manuscripts, 1973 (Box 14)
    - MARC Records, Conference on Use, Wisconsin Historical Society, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Michigan State (Box 15)
    - NEH Newspaper Panel, 1985 (Box 15)
    - NYC Consulting, December 1972 (Box 15)
    - OCLC AMC, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Oklahoma Forms (Box 15)
    - Paradigm, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Public Archives of Canada (Box 15)
    - Reference Librarian Article, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Roseman, Mindy, 1981 (Box 15)
    - Research Leave, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Rutgers, 1980 (Box 15)
    - Sizer, Samuel A., 1974 (Box 15)
    - SHARE Archives, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Smithsonian Systems (SIBIS) (Box 15)
    - Spindex Conference Proceedings (Box 15)
    - Spindex Report - Reviews (Box 15)
    - SPIRES, 1980 (Box 15)
    - Spindex Users' Network (SUN), 1981 (Box 15)
    - New England Archivists, Inc., 1975 (Box 15)
    - National Association of State Archives and Records Administrators (NASARA), 1977 (Box 15)
    - Syracuse Lecture (Box 15)
    - Thickman, Erica, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Winters, Joan M., 1975 (Box 15)
    - Technical Services (Box 15)
    - Rare Books Dept., 1989-1990 (Box 15)
    - Rare Books Dept. - Staffing, 1989 (Box 15)
    - Rare Books Dept., 1988-1989 (Box 15)
    - Presidential Councillors Luncheon - biographies, Oct. 3, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Olin/Stimson Space Planning Program, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Tejada, Suzana (Box 15)
    - Trustee/Council Weekend, 1988 (Box 15)
    - Special Collections Management, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
    - Special Collections Administration, 1989-90 (Box 15)
    - Silverman, Dennis, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Schiller, Anne Louise, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Samburg, Lorrie (Box 15)
    - Olin Library Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
      Restricted to permission of the donor and to the director of the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections
    - Lindemann, Richard, 1993 (Box 15)
    - Kemp, Carla, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Rabinowitz, Alan, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Karwan, Nan, 1991 (Box 15)
    - Johnson Grad School Campus Visit, April 1993 (Box 15)
    - Class of 1964 Visit, 1988 (Box 15)
    - History of Science Collections, 1988 (Box 15)
    - Icelandic Collection, 1988-1989 (Box 15)
    - Icelandic Collection, 1991 (Box 15)
    - Icelandic Collection, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
    - Icelandic Collection, 1992-1993 (Box 15)
    - Humphries, Julian M., Jr. (Box 15)
    - Hobbie, Margaret (Box 15)
    - Historical Resources Center, 1988 (Box 15)
    - Harm, Nancy, 1994 (Box 15)
    - Finch, Herbert, 1992-1996 (Box 15)
    - Eppard, Philip, 1993 (Box 15)
    - Corson, David, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 15)
    - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
    - Budget, Library (General), 1991 (Box 15)
    - Capital Equipment Requirements, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
    - AAP Visual Resource Steering Committee, 2003 (Box 16)
    - AAUP, 2003 (Box 16)
    - ACRL (Box 16)
    - ACRL Configuration, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Administrative Computing at Cornell, 2003 (Box 16)
    - ADS - Harvard - Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics, 2003 (Box 16)
    - Alumni and Friends Access, 2002 (Box 16)
    - American Anthropology Association, 2003 (Box 16)
    - Annual Report - CUL, 2003-04 (Box 16)
    - Annual Report - CUL, 2002-2003 (Box 16)
    - ARL Conference on Special Collections, 2000 (Box 16)
    - ARL Meeting, 1999 (Box 16)
    - arXiv (Box 16)
    - arXiv/TOP Partnership (Box 16)
    - Associate University Librarian for Library Information Technologies (AUL/LIT) Candidates, 2005 (Box 16)
    - arXiv (Box 16)
    - ARL - Kansas City (Box 16)
    - AR/MS (William) Study (Box 16)
    - Baker, Nicholson, 1994 (Box 16)
    - Brothers, Joyce, 2001 (Box 16)
    - Calhoun, Karen, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Campus Computing Directors (CCDs), 2005 (Box 16)
    - Catalyst, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Central Depositing Initiative, 2001 (Box 16)
    - Change Management, 2003 (Box 16)
    - Cornell Institute for Digital Collections (CIDC), 1999 (Box 16)
    - CIDC Presentation, 1997 (Box 16)
    - CIP, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Circulation Statistics (Box 16)
    - Cornell Information Technologies (CIT), 2005 (Box 16)
    - CIT, 2004 (Box 16)
    - CIT/Library Collaboration (Box 16)
    - CLIR (Box 16)
    - Coalition for Networked Information (CNI), 1999 (Box 16)
    - CNI Fall Meeting, 2001 (Box 16)
    - CNI San Antonio, 2000 (Box 16)
    - CNI Presentation - Portland, 2004 (Box 16)
    - Common Spot Implementation, 2005 (Box 16)
    - CNI Fall Meeting, 2004 (Box 16)
    - CNI December Meeting, 2003 (Box 16)
    - CNI Task Force Meeting, Washington D.C., 2005 (Box 16)
    - CNI Fall Meeting - Phoenix, AZ, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Columbia Univ. Conference, 2004 (Box 16)
    - Common Spot Implementation, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Compaq Computer Proposal (Box 16)
    - Computer World Award (Box 16)
    - Computer World / Smithsonian Awards (Box 16)
    - Communications and Media Relations, Director of (Box 16)
    - Computing and Information Science, 2001 (Box 16)
    - Congressional Testimony, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Cooke, Robert Project, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Copyright, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Copyright Service (Box 16)
    - Cornell Alumni Association System Presentation, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Cornell Budget, 2006-2007 (Box 16)
    - Course Management Systems, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Course Website Linking, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Creation Station Project, 2000 (Box 16)
    - C Theory Multimedia (Box 16)
    - CUL Public Affairs, 1999 (Box 16)
    - CUL Advisory Council, 2004 (Box 16)
    - CUL Budget, 2005 (Box 16)
    - CUL Goals and Objectives, 2002 (Box 16)
    - CUL Master Plan, 2001-2006 (Box 16)
    - CUL Priorities, 2005-2006 (Box 16)
    - CUP/CUL Proposal (Box 16)
    - Digital Consulting and Production Services (DCAPS) (Box 16)
    - DCAPS, 2003 (Box 16)
    - DCAPS and Digital Media Group (DMG), 2004 (Box 16)
    - DCAPS President, SAA, 2004 (Box 16)
    - DCAPS Semiannual Report, 2004-05 (Box 17)
    - Desktop Services (DLIT), 2004 (Box 16)
    - Desktop IT Security, 2004 (Box 16)
    - Desktop Services - Future Plans (Box 16)
    - Digital Asset Management, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Digital Asset Management Systems inc. Michigan Request for Proposal (RFP), 2002 (Box 16)
    - Digital Collectives in Indigenous Cultures, 2001 (Box 16)
    - Digital Collections Management, 2004 (Box 16)
    - "Digital Cornucopia" Sun Frankfurt Presentation (Box 17)
    - Digital Futures Plan, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Digital Image Collections Rep, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Digital Libraries, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Digital Library Technology, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Digital Media Group, 2004-05 (Box 17)
    - Digital Preservation Framework, CUL (Box 17)
    - Digital Preservation (Box 17)
    - Digital Preservation Meeting, 2004 (Box 17)
    - Digital Repository - Catherwood Library, 2004 (Box 17)
    - Digital Services (Box 17)
    - Digital Synergies Group, 2004 (Box 17)
    - Digitization, Report of Task Force on Selection, 2004 (Box 17)
    - Digitization Service, 2002-2003 (Box 17)
    - Dimunation, Mark, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Distance Learning, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Digital Library Federation (DLF), 2004-2005 (Box 17)
    - DLF Aquifer (Box 17)
    - DLF Strategic Planning Session, 2003 (Box 17)
    - DLF Spring Forum, 2000 (Box 17)
    - DLF Strategic Planning, 2003 (Box 17)
    - Digital Library Federation, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Digital Library and Information Technologies (DLIT) Budget, 2004-2005 (Box 17)
    - DLIT Administration, 1999 (Box 17)
    - DLIT Budgeting, 2005-2006 (Box 17)
    - DLIT Facilities, 2005-2006 (Box 17)
    - DLIT Management, 2002 (Box 17)
    - DLIT, 1999 (Box 17)
    - DLIT Servers, 2002 (Box 17)
    - DPubs Conference, 2004 (Box 17)
    - DPubs Development Project, 2004 (Box 17)
    - DPubs/Information Strategies (Box 17)
    - DSpace Federation, 2002 (Box 17)
    - Duplication in the General College, 2003 (Box 17)
    - EAD Project (Box 17)
    - Ebner, Susan (Box 17)
    - Edinburgh Search (Box 17)
    - Edinburgh, University of, 2003 (Box 17)
    - Editors' Forum, 2003 (Box 17)
    - EDUCAUSE, 2003 (Box 17)
    - E-Books, 2003 (Box 17)
    - EDUCAUSE - Orlando, FL, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Ehling, Tracy, 2003 (Box 17)
    - Electronic Journals (Box 17)
    - Electronic Document Delivery (Box 17)
    - Electronic Publishing, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Electronic Publishing Priority #7, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Electronic Records Project (Box 17)
    - Electronic Publishing Directory Search (Box 17)
    - Electronic Resources, 1998 (Box 17)
    - Electronic Student Records Rep., 2000 (Box 17)
    - Elsevier IR Study, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Electronic Mathematics Archiving Network Initiative (EMANI), 2003 (Box 17)
    - EMANI - Meeting in Gottingen, 2002 (Box 17)
    - EMANI - NSF/DEG Proposal (Box 17)
    - EMPSL Libraries, 2002 (Box 17)
    - ENCompass, 2002 (Box 17)
    - ENCompass Development, 2002 (Box 17)
    - Endeavor Information Systems, 1998 (Box 17)
    - EPIC (Columbia) / CIAO (Box 17)
    - ERC Tokyo, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Euclid Article, 2001 (Box 18)
    - Euclid Amsterdam Trip, 2003 (Box 18)
    - Euclid Board Meeting, 2003 (Box 18)
    - Euclid Governing Board Meeting, 2002 (Box 18)
    - Euclid / Mellon Report, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Faculty Advisory Board on Information Technologies (FABIT), 2002 (Box 18)
    - FABIT, 2003-04 (Box 18)
    - FABIT - Network Review (Box 18)
    - Faculty Grants for Digital Library (Box 18)
    - FABIT, 1999 (Box 18)
    - Faculty Innovation in Teaching Grants, 2003 (Box 18)
    - Faculty Innovation in Teaching Grants Program, 2002 (Box 18)
    - First Person Cornell (Box 18)
    - Frick Collection, 1998 (Box 18)
    - Fundraising (Library), 2005 (Box 18)
    - "Future of the Archive" Presentation - Edinburgh, 2002 (Box 18)
    - Gagnon, Deborah, 2002 (Box 18)
    - GloPAS / IMLS, 2003-2004 (Box 18)
    - GloPAC / GloPAD (Box 18)
    - Gortner Study / Cornell IT, 2003 (Box 18)
    - Gateway Redesign (Box 18)
    - Gay, Geri, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Ginspurg & the E-Print Archive, 2000 (Box 18)
    - GloPAC, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Glorious to View, 2004 (Box 18)
    - Goals and Objectives, 2002-2007 (Box 18)
    - Goldsen Archives, 2003 (Box 18)
    - Google / Cornell, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Groxis, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Harvest (Project), 2001 (Box 18)
    - Handhelds (Box 18)
    - University of Hertfordshire Higher Education Digitisation Service (HEDS), 2002 (Box 18)
    - Hillmann, Diane, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Hillmann, Diane, 2006-07 (Box 18)
    - HP Labs, 2003 (Box 18)
    - History Makers Proposal, 2004 (Box 18)
    - Humanities Rep.- Cornell (Box 18)
    - Huntington Free Library, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Huntington Free Library (Box 18)
    - Huntington Free Library, 2005 (Box 18)
    - International Council on Archives (ICA), 2001 (Box 18)
    - ICA - FIDA Group (Box 18)
    - ICA Documents / St. Petersburg Meeting, 2003 (Box 18)
    - ICA - Beijing Meeting, 2002 (Box 18)
    - ICA / Conference Internationale de la Table Ronde des Archives (CITRA) Meeting, 1999 (Box 18)
    - ICA / CITRA, 2000 (Box 18)
    - ICA, 2003 (Box 18)
    - ICA Executive Board Meeting - Washington D.C., 2005 (Box 18)
    - ICA / CITRA, 2003 (Box 18)
    - ICA - Fund for International Archival Development (FIDA), 2004 (Box 18)
    - ICA - Iraq, 2003 (Box 18)
    - ICA - CITRA, 2003 (Box 18)
    - ICA Meeting at SAA, 2005 (Box 18)
    - ICA - Task Force on Revenue, 2005 (Box 18)
    - ICA / UNESCO - China, 2003 (Box 18)
    - ICA - Washington Meeting, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Icelandic Proposal, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Icelandic Exhibition, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Icelandic Studies Electronic Journal, 2002 (Box 18)
    - IT Managers Council (ITMC), 2004 (Box 18)
    - Informed Strategies, 2004 (Box 18)
    - IT Security (Cornell), 2003 (Box 18)
    - IFUP, 2003 (Box 18)
    - Image Projects (Cornell), 1999 (Box 18)
    - Information Technology Review Campuswide (OIT/CIT), 2003 (Box 18)
    - IMG, 1999 (Box 18)
    - Institute of Museum and Library Studies (IMLS), 2003 (Box 18)
    - Inclusion Initiative (Box 18)
    - In Common, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Integrated Framework, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Intellectual Property Issues, 2001 (Box 18)
    - Internal Grant Program, 2002 (Box 18)
    - Intel Grant (Box 18)
    - International New Media Art, 2002 (Box 18)
    - IQPC Digital Rights Management Conference, 2001 (Box 18)
    - Iraq, 2003 (Box 18)
    - IT Workforce Planning, Campus / Library (Box 18)
    - International Records Management Trust (IRMT) (Box 18)
    - Information Technology Collaboration (ITMC), 2004 (Box 18)
    - ITMC, 2005 (Box 19)
    - ITSO - Cornell University Library (CUL), 2005 (Box 19)
    - Islandica, 2001 (Box 19)
    - Janus Conference #6 (Box 19)
    - Jackson, Laura, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Jackson, Petrina, 2003 (Box 19)
    - Janus Conference, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Johnson Museum, 2003 (Box 19)
    - J-STAGE (Box 19)
    - Kay, Bill, 1996 (Box 19)
    - Korea / Vietnam Memorial Rededication Committee, 2002 (Box 19)
    - Korea / Vietnam Memorial Rededication Committee, 2003 (Box 19)
    - Kuo, Melissa, 2004 (Box 19)
    - KVRF, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Library and Related Information Services (LARIS) (Box 19)
    - LARIS - Digital Repository Study, 2003 (Box 19)
    - Law Enforcement Access to Library Records, CUL Task Force, 2002 (Box 19)
    - Lawrence, Dan H. Papers, 1997 (Box 19)
    - Law Library, 2000 (Box 19)
    - LC / Cornell Project, 1999 (Box 19)
    - LC / CLIR / Cornell Project (Box 19)
    - Learning & Teaching with Technology Expo, 2003 (Box 19)
    - Lehman's College Engagement, 2003 (Box 19)
    - Levy, David, 1999 (Box 19)
    - Library Advisory Council, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
    - Library Budget Reductions, 2003 (Box 19)
    - Library Gateway Report, 1999 (Box 19)
    - Library (CUL) History (Box 19)
    - Library Management Systems, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Library Management Systems, Director of, 2001 (Box 19)
    - Library Workforce Planning, 2003 (Box 19)
    - Liberty Hyde Bailey Project, 2003 (Box 19)
    - Library / CS Collaboration, 1997 (Box 19)
    - Life Science Working Group Report, 2004 (Box 19)
    - Lindseth, Jon, 1999 (Box 19)
    - LMS Demonstrations, 1998 (Box 19)
    - LIBQUAL - CUL, 2001-2003 (Box 19)
    - LMS Steering Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 19)
    - Library Management Team (LMT), 1999-2000 (Box 19)
    - LMT, 1998-1999 (Box 19)
    - LMT Goals & Objectives, 2004-2005 (Box 19)
    - LMT Priorities Review, 2004 (Box 19)
    - LMT - Strategic Priorities, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
    - Luna Insight, 2003 (Box 19)
    - U. of Manitoba, 2005 (Box 19)
    - McGill Consultation, 1999 (Box 19)
    - Manitoba, U. of, Consulting, 2004 (Box 19)
    - Models for Academic Support (MAS), 2010 (Box 19)
    - MAS E-Publishing, 2010 (Box 19)
    - MAS Final Rep., 2010 (Box 19)
    - Mass Digitization, 2004 (Box 19)
    - Master Plan, 2002 (Box 19)
    - Math ARC (Box 19)
    - Mellow Foundation Digital Archiving, 2001 (Box 19)
    - Mellow Foundation Planning Grant, "A New Role for Res. Libraries", 2002 (Box 19)
    - Mellow / Icelandic Proposal, 2000 (Box 19)
    - Minnesota, University Library (Box 19)
    - Microsoft, 1999 (Box 19)
    - MOA (Box 19)
    - Monash Univ., Australia, 2003 (Box 19)
    - Modern Language Association Report on the Future of Scholarly Publishing, 2002 (Box 19)
    - Multimedia Trends Report, 2001 (Box 19)
    - MyLibrary, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Nabokov Papers, 2001 (Box 19)
    - NARA: Annual Reports, 2004 (Box 19)
    - NARA / ERA (Box 19)
    - Native American Collection, 2005 (Box 19)